BGM
Please subscribe to our channel.
The theme of the song is about duality.
The theme of the song is about the duality between something that is cute or beautiful and something that has a bit of a spine.
I don't want to sing too much, but I'd like to sing a little bit more.
I don't want to sing too hard.
Not too much?
Yes, I do.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, sir.
I'm feeling a little overheated.
I'll try to keep it down.
If we could just slow it down a little bit...
I might be able to cool it down a little more.
Let's try it dry.
Let's cool it down a little bit.
I'd like you to be fed up.
It's too slow.
Rather than singing with a lot of passion...
I was told to sing with a little bit of restraint.
So that was a little bit different from how I interpreted it.
I'd like to do my best to adjust the interpretation for the live performance.
I'll do my best for the live performance.
I'm nervous.
Thank you very much.
me
hmm...
I'll dance more beautifully than anyone else!
I'm going to dance more beautifully than anyone else.
I'll take it. I'll regret it.
Thank you very much. Well, it's all right, I'm glad you're here.
One moment, please.
Oh...
I'm just wondering if you could help me with a couple of choruses or a jamo or something.
That's not your thing.
Really? I don't get that impression at all.
Really?
In fact, everyone at Ameflash does it so well.
It's always a big help.
Really?
I can't remember the pitch of the hamo.
I guess I'm pretty good on the spot for someone who can't remember.
That's great.
If that's the case...
I don't think I'll have a hard time at all.
Really?
I'm glad.
I'm counting on you.
Oh, my God.
It would have been bad if it were true.
It's a great match.
I'm going for the second one.
Thank you very much.
I think that's all.
I think you should be aware that it's a very special skill to be able to listen to a guide like this and say it's expensive once and be able to do it.
Really?
Not many people can do it right away.
I'm glad.
I think it's great that you all can do it so well.
Harmonizing with confidence
I finished with a good feeling
Yes, I think it's good that we got all the shots
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry, I've said it many times.
No, no, no, no, no. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
The way we recorded this song was quite different from the way we recorded the other songs.
We recorded the whole song one by one.
It was the first time for me to do it that way, so I practiced it at home for a long time.
I think I was able to show some of the results of my practice at home, so it was a very enjoyable recording.
I thought I was praised.
I was praised.
When I get compliments, I can't say anything but "thank you" with my hands.
It made me really happy.
It really made me want to practice harder.
By the way, there was something that bothered me.
When you were recording, what did you buy the cups of coffee that you brought together?
When I held it in my hand and brought it to my mouth...
I bought a string of tea tea.
I thought it was so cute.
I've done that a lot.
I had nothing to do with it.
Yes, sir.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
You're beautiful, you're beautiful, you're beautiful, you don't know anything
It's not easy
Don't tell anyone
Don't tell anyone you're beautiful
It's not easy
Thank you very much. It was perfect.
I was a bit tempted to get excited at the "If you still like it" part, but I suppressed it a bit,
I want to make it look rather simple here, too.
Once you see it
Once you see it, you can't go back.
Once you see it, there's no going back.
You're right.
If you're still willing, I'll open the secret door now.
Yes, thank you. This place was perfect.
That's all for the main-like line. Thank you very much.
I'd like to ask for your help with a little bit of a hamo kind of thing,
First of all, hey is going to go down on the intro.
I'll check the timing once.
I'll try.
Here it is.
Let's go one more time.
It's not working.
I don't know.
To be honest, I don't really care where the timing is.
Well, well, well, well.
It's perfect.
Thank you.
Yes, it's fine.
Oh, it's perfect.
That's all.
Yes, thank you.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
I thought it would be difficult when I first received the sound files,
But I learned how to voice trade and listened to the tentative songs by myself,
I was able to imitate them and sing in my own way,
But when I came here, it was a little different, a little softer,
I was asked to sing in a way that wasn't too strong,
I thought it would be difficult, but I was able to enjoy it.
I'm the type of person who can't do that.
So it's going really well, so I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do it.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to handle it.
So rather than just doing it right away, I'd rather get it and do it once at home.
I'd like to try it at home.
I can't do it if I don't know what I'm doing.
I'm not sure if it's ready or not.
But I don't have any lines, so I don't really want to
It's a calm song like this.
When I first heard the tentative song, I was really surprised.
I thought, "What's this?
There's no going back now.
I'm most curious about who's there.
No, no, no!
What a waste of a song!
Apologize!
You're being filmed.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Like this.
I'm Hana here too.
No one can help it. The secret's out...
Kanue Sumi...
I'll show you.
That was really good.
I'll take this one.
Here you go.
It's been taken.
It's in.
Poke-poke-poke.
Thank you very much.
The lines are scattered.
It's so good. I'll take one of these too, please.
It looks super nice. Thank you very much.
That's all. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Good work.
That was quick.
I didn't have any humor, so I finished early.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
The song was really difficult and I had a hard time with Waytrade too.
I had a hard time with Waytrade, too, but this was a totally different way of singing from Waytrade, so it was
It was very difficult for me.
The reason why I did it was
I'm really bad at English pronunciation.
English has been appearing in a lot of lyrics recently.
I didn't have a great teacher to help me there too.
I've heard stories.
Also, it was really hard for me to get the pitch
I couldn't get the "wisdom" part at all.
I'm trying to do it a little bit slower.
Slowly.
I practiced in slow motion.
I think I'm getting it.
Hmm...
Hm...
I think it's done.
Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry it's been three hours.
I was bored out of my mind.
If you touch me, you'll hurt yourself.
If it still hurts, I'll just do it.
Be prepared for anything.
Pandara in her true form... dangerous...
That's a nice touch.
Only the endings are a little too straight now with "sugatā" and "pandora".
So I'm going to use "Sugataa" and "Pandora".
I'd like to make it a bit messy, or add some color.
Great, thank you very much!
The song part
I think it would be better if it was a bit fluffy or something.
Yes!
If you still like it, I'll open the secret door now!
It was a nice touch!
I think that's all.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
You couldn't push it.
You can't push?
No, I can't.
That's good.
But I wish we could have stayed for detention.
I wanted to stay until they said it was over.
That's right.
But it's not the same as when I was in voice training.
And the way I've been practicing.
The way I've been practicing has changed a lot.
I'm going to do it for the show.
It was very difficult for me to do it all at once today.
It's very difficult.
I've been waiting for a while.
I've been waiting a long time.
Well, I wanted to go home and practice before coming.
I wanted to bring it in once.
It was difficult, but...
I'm looking forward to seeing it finished.
I've been doing the rapping for a while now.
I've been doing some lax stuff when I'm recording.
I'm going to rap basically.
I thought it was difficult to rap and sing in a totally different way.
I thought it was very difficult.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Are you still there?
Just until the correction is finished.
Shall we go home?
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to our channel.